Finding Aid for Michigan Union Publications, 1905-ongoing.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan Union Publications 1905-[ongoing], 1908-1990
Michigan Union.
2.5 linear feet
0515 Bimu F15 2
Publications of the Michigan Union includes miscellaneous annual reports, brochures, constitutions, directories, histories, manuals, newsletters, organizational charts, programs, regulations, reprints, schedules of the Michigan Union; as well as musical scores and programs from the Michigan Union Opera, Mimes, and Musket productions.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The publications are received periodically from the unit (Donor # 2024 ).
The publications are open to research.
See the history in the finding aid for Michigan Union records.
Publications of the Michigan Union includes miscellaneous annual reports, brochures, constitutions, directories, histories, manuals, newsletters, organizational charts, programs, regulations, reprints, schedules of the Michigan Union; as well as musical scores and programs from the Michigan Union Opera, Mimes, and Musket productions. The Publications series is divided into two subseries: Unit Publications and Sub-Unit Publications
Subjects:
Michigan Union.; Michigan Union Opera.; Mimes (University of Michigan); Musket (University of Michigan); University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs.; University of Michigan--Choral organizations.; M handbook.; Michiganetiquette.
Contributors:
College musicals--University of Michigan.; Michigan Union Opera.; Mimes (University of Michigan); Musket (University of Michigan)
Genre Terms:
Annual reports.; Pamphlets.; Constitutions.; Directories.; Histories.; Manuals.; Newsletters.; Organizational charts.; Programs.; Regulations.; Reprints.; Schedules.; Scores.
- Printed Materials
  - Unit Publications
    The Unit Publications subseries includes newsletters, directories, and manuals relating to the building of and the daily activities of the Michigan Union.
    - Annual Reports 1912-1913 (Box 1)
    - Brochures
      - General 1917-1992 (Box 1)
      - A Brief Story of the Michigan Union
        - 1915 (Box 1)
        - 1921 (Box 1)
      - The Michigan Union Building, circa 1921 (Box 1)
      - The Michigan Union for Michigan Men, undated (Box 1)
      - The Plan and Purpose of the Michigan Union, circa 1905 (Box 1)
      - University of Michigan Union, 1904 (Box 1)
      - University of Michigan Union: for University Men Everywhere, circa 1915 (Box 1)
    - Constitutions
      - 1909-1920 (Box 1)
    - Directories
      - Subscribers to the Building Fund of the University of Michigan Union, 1916 (Box 1)
      - Unfinished Business--The Michigan Union Building: List of Alumni Who Have Subscribed Nothing, 1919 (Box 1)
      - Unfinished Business--The Michigan Union Building: List of Subscribing Alumni by Classes, 1919 (Box 1)
    - Histories
      - The Michigan Union: Its Evolution, [1979] (Box 1)
      - Story Without End: The History of the University of Michigan Union, 1903-1954, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Manuals
      - M Handbook
        - 1947-1954 (Box 1)
        - 1956-1959 (Box 1)
      - Michiganetiquette
        - circa 1943-1944 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters
      - Campus News
        - 1944 (Box 1)
        - 1945 v.2 (Box 1)
      - Continuum
        - 1985-1988 (Box 1)
      - Michigan Union Bulletin: Issued Only to Chairmen and Members of Michigan Union Committees, 1915 (Box 1)
      - Michigan Union Reports
        - 1960-1963 (Box 1)
      - Michigan Union Update
        - 1981 (Box 1)
      - Panorama
        - 1945 (Box 1)
      - The Union Bulletin
        - 1933-1936 (Box 1)
      - The Union Daily Bulletin
        - 1933
          - March (Box 1)
          - April (Box 1)
          - May (Box 1)
        - 1935
          - November (Box 1)
          - December (Box 1)
        - 1936
          - March (Box 1)
          - April (Box 1)
      - Union Notes
        - 1987-1988 v.1 (Box 1)
        - 1988-1989 v.2 (Box 1)
        - 1989-1990 v.3 (Box 1)
      - The Union Review
        - 1934-1935 v.4 (Box 1)
        - 1935-1936 v.5 (Box 1)
    - Organizational Charts
      - Organization Plan: University of Michigan Union, 1917-1918 (Box 1)
    - Programs 1933 (Box 1)
    - Questionnaires
      - Michigan Union-North Campus Commons Organizational Assessment, undated (Box 1)
    - Regulations
      - General Information Booklet, 1931 (Box 1)
      - Handbook of Rules and Regulations, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Reprints
      - University of Michigan Union, Ann Arbor, 1921 (Box 1)
    - Schedules
      - Class Schedule 1985 (Box 1)
  - Sub-Unit Publications
    The Sub-Unit Publications subseries includes printed material from sub-units within the Michigan Union, such as MUSKET (Michigan Union Show, Ko-Eds Too), Project Community, and the Ticket Office. In addition, there is a complete collection of musical scores and programs from the productions of MUSKET's predecessor, the Michigan Union Opera, or MIMES.
    - Michigan Union Opera (Mimes)
      - Musical Scores
        - Michigenda, 1908 (Box 1)
        - Culture, 1908 (Box 1)
        - Koanzaland, 1909 (Box 1)
        - The Crimson Chest, 1910 (Box 1)
        - The Awakened Ramses, 1911 (includes Script) (Box 2)
        - Contrarie Mary, 1913 (Box 2)
        - A Model Daughter, 1914 (Box 2)
        - All That Glitters, 1915 (Box 2)
        - Tres Rouge, 1916 (Box 2)
        - Fool's Paradise, 1917 (Box 2)
        - Let's Go Over Here Over There, 1918 (Box 2)
        - Come on, Dad, 1919 (Box 2)
        - George Did It, 1920 (Box 2)
        - Top O' Th' Mornin', 1921 (Box 2)
        - Make It for Two, 1921 (Box 2)
        - In and Out, 1922 (Box 2)
        - Cotton Stockings, 1923 (Box 2)
        - Tickled to Death, 1925 (Box 2)
        - Tambourine, 1925 (Box 2)
        - Front Page Stuff, 1926 (Box 2)
        - The Same to You, 1927 (Box 2)
        - Lace it Up, 1950 (Box 2)
        - Never too Late, 1952 (Box 2)
        - No Cover Charge, 1952 (Box 2)
        - Up 'N' Atom, 1952 (Box 2)
        - Hail to Victor, 1954 (Box 2)
        - Film Flam, 1955 (Box 2)
      - Programs
        - 1908-1910 (Box 2)
        - 1911-1915 (Box 2)
        - 1916-1920 (Box 2)
        - 1921-1925 (Box 2)
        - 1926-1930 (Box 2)
        - 1931-1935 (Box 2)
        - 1936-1940 (Box 2)
        - 1941-1945 (Box 2)
        - 1946-1950 (Box 2)
        - 1951-1955 (Box 2)
      - Sheet Music
        (stored in outsize box)
        - Michigenda, 1908 (Box 3)
          (includes 9 songs)
        - Culture, 1908 (Box 3)
          (includes 10 songs)
        - Koanzaland, 1909 (Box 3)
        - The Crimson Chest, 1910 (Box 3)
          (includes 6 songs)
        - The Awakened Ramses, 1911 (Box 3)
          (includes 2 songs)
        - Contrarie Mary, 1913 (Box 3)
        - A Model Daughter, 1914 (Box 3)
        - All That Glitters, 1915 (Box 3)
        - Tres Rouge, 1916 (Box 3)
        - Fool's Paradise, 1917 (Box 3)
        - Let's Go Over Here Over There, 1918 (Box 3)
        - Come on, Dad, 1919 (Box 3)
        - George Did It, 1920 (Box 3)
        - Top O' Th' Mornin', 1921 (Box 3)
    - Musket (Michigan Union Show, Ko-EDS Too)
      - Programs
        - 1956-1960 (Box 2)
        - 1961-1965 1967 (Box 2)
    - Project Community
      - Brochures 1985-1989 (Box 2)
    - Ticket Office
      - Flyers 1990 (Box 2)